

# Bung-Jin Lee

(616) 802-0570 Byung2523@gmail.com Kentwood, Michigan 49508

# **SUMMARY**

Career change to gain exposure and experience in the tech field of Front-end development or Full Stack development. Hardworking and reliable individual with strong ability in web development. Offering Front and Back-end development, highly organized, proactive and punctual with team-oriented mentality.

#### **SKILLS**

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, J-query, DOM, AJAX
- React, bootstrap
- Visual Studio Code
- Git + GitHub, Command Line
- Node.js, Express.js
- NPM, API
- PostgreSQL, Mysql
- Amazon Web Services
- Heroku
- Production/Deployment
- Debugging proficiency

- Friendly, positive attitude
- WordPress
- CMS platforms
- Microsoft Office
- Organization
- Project planning
- Problem resolution
- People skills
- Time management
- Customer service
- Troubleshooting
- First Aid/CPR

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Wellness Coach-MOD

Wyoming, MI

YMCA Spartan Nash/Oct 2016 to Current

- Provide excellent member service by greeting and acknowledge all members to encourage wellness participation.
- Monitor the wellness center as fitness members use the equipment to ensure their general safety and equipment function.
- Demonstrates correct stances, posture, alignment and technique during wellness consultation.
- Accurately uses scheduling software to enter in staff member availability, member appointments and all other data necessary.
- Assisted clients with identifying and pursuing different health and wellness objectives.
- Developed and maintained excellent member relationships to promote facility offerings and assist with health or exercise questions.

### Co-Head Coach

Grand Rapids, MI

West Catholic High School/Mar 2020 to Current

- Encouraged team members to become stronger, more agile athletes and more successful competitors through focus, effective training and proper nutrition.
- Checked equipment and monitored common areas to maintain proper upkeep

while remaining vigilant on safety.

- Monitored players' academic progress to ensure continuous success and commitment to education.
- Ran drills and fitness circuits to improve athletes' coordination and skills.
- Reviewed game tapes of competitor events to understand strategies and plan approaches.

# Freelance Web Developer

Grand Rapids, MI

Self-employed/Feb 2019 to Current

- Created web materials such as images and redirect links for use in marketing and email campaigns.
- Crafted mobile-friendly websites and transitioned legacy site to mobile-friendly platform.
- Checked all sites and online elements for proper adherence to brand guidelines and functionality.
- Built and applied reusable code to other projects to reduce consulting fees and development hours.

#### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

Bachelor of Science: Exercise Science Western Michigan University Dec 2015 Kalamazoo, MI

Bachelor of CIS Web and Mobile development: Computer and Information Sciences
Davenport University 2018
Grand Rapids, MI

# WEBSITES, PORTFOLIOS, PROFILES

- https://byung2523.github.io/Basic-Portfolio/
- https://github.com/byung2523